<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>GitJournal</title>
    <link>https://gitjournal.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on GitJournal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gitjournal.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/about-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/about-us/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re a small company based in Barcelona, Spain; who care a lot about Privacy, Data Portability and making Self-Hosting more accessible.
 Drop us an email at hello@gitjournal.io</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>This privacy policy is designed to provide transparency to your use of the GitJournal applications. This application allows you to write and manage notes.
User provided information If you request information or technical support, your personal data (such as your email address) is used only to respond to specific inquiry. The other information such as application version, device and OS version is required only for improving the application.
Information gathering and usage GitJournal also collects aggregated, anonymous user data regarding app usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/support/</guid>
      <description>Please email support@gitjournal.io for personalized support
FAQ How do you plan to sustain this project? Sustaining an Open Source Project can be challenging in the long term. The idea with GitJournal is to be a 100% Open Source Project - No Open Core model. Here are our current ideas on how to sustain this in the long term -
 Paid Pro Version - Some Advanced features could require payment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>