<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo Tailwind Starter on GitJournal</title>
    <link>https://gitjournal.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hugo Tailwind Starter on GitJournal</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://gitjournal.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GitJournal May Update</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/blog/2020-06-12-may-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/blog/2020-06-12-may-update/</guid>
      <description>GitJournal is a mobile first note taking application integrated with Git. It’s based on the idea that you should have control over your data, and that we all have multiple devices in our daily lives, and therefore need to be in control of the mechanism to synchronize our notes across these devices.
Git was chosen as the method to do so, as there are already many commercial provides of Git, and setting up your own Git Server has a much lower barrier to entry than any other setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! My name is Vishesh. I&amp;rsquo;m the author of GitJournal. I&amp;rsquo;ve been writing open source software for over a decade, and care a lot about data privacy and making it more accessible to the rest of the world.
Long before I started GitJournal, I had been storing my notes and journal entries in plain text or markdown files. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple everlasting format that works with almost all editors. What was lacking was a way to synchronize my notes over multiple devices, while still having control of my data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contribute</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/contribute/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/contribute/</guid>
      <description>GitJournal is an Open Souce project, and can always use the help.
You can help via -
 Translating GitJournal Voting on Existing Issues Requesting new Features Donating via Paypal  Additionally, if GitJournal has been useful for you, please tell others about it or post about it on your favorite site.
Feel free to send me an email at feedback@gitjournal.io</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End User License Agreement</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/apple_eula/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/apple_eula/</guid>
      <description>GitJournal End User License Agreement
This End User License Agreement (“Agreement”) is between you and GitJournal and governs use of this app made available through the Apple App Store. By installing the GitJournal App, you agree to be bound by this Agreement and understand that there is no tolerance for objectionable content. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this Agreement, you are not entitled to use the GitJournal App.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foam</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/docs/apps/foam/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/docs/apps/foam/</guid>
      <description>You can easily use GitJournal on your mobile / tablet, along with Foam on the desktop. In fact Foam recommends GitJournal as the recommended mobile app. Both projects are in contact with each other to ensure they work well together.
+
How to Sync?   Manually - You may use git commands from the terminal or directly from within Foam.
  Automatically - You can install git-auto-sync in order to monitor certain folders and automatically commit and push the changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joplin Import</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/docs/import/joplin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/docs/import/joplin/</guid>
      <description>Joplin is an awesome note taking app, unfortunately it uses its own custom JEX format, instead of the more standard Markdown format, and therefore cannot be used with GitJournal. However, Joplin does support exporting your notes to markdown.
Instructions   File -&amp;gt; Export -&amp;gt; Markdown
  Copy the markdown files to your existing Git Repo Folder
  Related  Why use the Markdown format? How to setup automatic syncing?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/newsletter/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Page</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/page/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/page/</guid>
      <description>This is a page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pricing</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/pricing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/pricing/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/privacy/</guid>
      <description>This privacy policy is designed to provide transparency to your use of the GitJournal applications. This application allows you to write and manage notes.
User provided information If you request information or technical support, your personal data (such as your email address) is used only to respond to specific inquiry. The other information such as application version, device and OS version is required only for improving the application.
Information gathering and usage GitJournal also collects aggregated, anonymous user data regarding app usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Support</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/support/</guid>
      <description>Please email me at support@gitjournal.io for any questions.
FAQ General Why create another Note Taking App? There are many Note taking apps on the desktop, but the mobile space is lacking good note taking apps which give you control over your data and operate with open protocols.
What is Git and why should I care? We all have many different devices. Our notes need to be accessible on all these devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms and Conditions</title>
      <link>https://gitjournal.io/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gitjournal.io/terms/</guid>
      <description>By downloading or using the app, these terms will automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, but not our trademarks in any way. The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright, database rights and other intellectual property rights related to it, still belong to Vishesh Handa.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>